tfmetalsreport.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | TF Metals Report

Welcome to [www.tfmetalsreport.com](http://www.tfmetalsreport.com/) (the " **Website** ").

This Website is operated by Buyapension.com, LLC (sometimes referred to as " **we** ," " **us** ," " **our** ").

By using this Website or any related app or service operated by us (the " **Services** " and, for clarity, all references in this Privacy Policy to “Services” includes the "Premium Services" as described in the Terms), you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy as well as other terms and policies as described in our Terms of Use available at <https://www.tfmetalsreport.com/legal> (the " **Terms** "). All references to "you" mean you, an individual. However, if you are using the Services or any related app or service on behalf of a business entity, then "you" means both you and your business entity.

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, then do not use the Services.

##  INFORMATION WE COLLECT

###  Anonymous Data

As a result of your use of the Services we may collect (or you may provide to us) information which is not personal in nature and which may not be used to identify you as a specific individual or business (" **Anonymous Data** ").

###  Personal Data

As a result of your use of the Services we may collect (or you may provide to us) the following types of information (" **Personal Data** "):

  * **User Account Information** : User names, nicknames, valid email addresses, passwords, post signatures, timezone locations, and similar types of information.
  * **User Profile Information** : Photos, avatars, your name, business name, job titles, industries where employed, location, physical addresses, website addresses, contact email addresses, phone numbers, social media accounts, personal biographies, videos, and similar types of information.
  * **Payment Information** : Payment information including credit/debit card numbers, account numbers, payment addresses, and similar types of information.
  * **Information We Collect Automatically** : We may collect information about you automatically, including your IP address, operating system, browser ID, browsing activity, time stamps, site navigation, button clicks, and similar types of information. We may also use and/or collect cookies and other types of data files (such as web beacons and cookie-equivalent technology), some of which may be stored on your computer or electronic device for use when you use the Services.
  * **Your Content** : You may also voluntarily provide information to us through the Services and also through other communication channels, including content, text, photos, videos, audio files, and similar types of information.

##  HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

###  Anonymous Data

We may use Anonymous Data for any purpose not otherwise prohibited by applicable law, without your consent, without providing notice to you, and without providing compensation to you, including without limitation sharing and selling Anonymous Data to third parties.

###  Personal Data

We will not share or sell your Personal Data expect as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy or the Terms.

However, we may use your Personal Data as follows:

  * **Sharing with Other Users** : We may share your Personal Data with other users of the Services including your posts, comments, and similar items, and if you communicate directly with other users, then we may share those communications with those other users which you choose to communicate with.
  * **Customization of Services** : We may use your Personal Data to customize and/or enhance your use of the Services.
  * **Advertising** : We may use your Personal Data to serve more customized ads to you on the Services.
  * **Communications** : We may use your Personal Data to send communications to you, including marketing communications.
  * **Payments** : If you purchase goods or services through our Services, then we may use your Personal Data to process your purchase and payment.
  * **Sharing with Affiliates & Third Parties**: We may share your Personal Data with our affiliates and other third parties to accomplish the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms of Use. This includes sharing your Personal Data with third party payments processors.
  * **Retention** : We may store and retain your Personal Data for purposes of using it as described in this Privacy Policy. However, we do not have any obligation to store your Personal Data for the benefit of you or any other third party.
  * **Per our Terms of Use** : We may use your Personal Data as provided in your Terms of Use.

###  Improvements to the Services

If you share ideas or suggestions with us regarding how to improve or modify our Services, then we may use all of the same without your consent, without providing notice to you, and without providing compensation to you.

###  Compliance with Legal Process

We may use and/or share your Personal Data as follows: (a) to comply with court orders, valid discovery requests, valid subpoenas, and other appropriate legal mechanisms; (b) to respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; (c) to prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding; (d) with our representatives and advisors, including attorneys and accountants; and/or (e) if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use or to investigate or prevent illegal or immoral actions.

###  Aggregated Data

We may aggregate your Personal Data with information we have about other users, individuals, and business, for the purpose of converting your Personal Data into Anonymous Data. Once converted, we may use that information as provided in this Privacy Policy.

##  YOUR CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION

###  Account Settings

Some of the information you provide to us may be changed or deleted by you in your account settings (or by emailing us at tfmetalsreport[at]gmail[dot]com). However, even if you change or delete that information, we may retain previous versions of the information for a reasonable period of time in order to continue providing the Services.

###  Cookies & Tracking Data

You may restrict our ability to use cookies and certain other types of data files by adjusting the settings on your device or browser.

###  Deleting Your Data

You may request that we delete your Personal Data from the Services by emailing us at tfmetalsreport[at]gmail[dot]com, but we do not have any obligation to honor that request. If you terminate your user account in accordance with our Terms of Use, then we will use reasonable efforts to remove your information from the sections of the Services that allow other users to see and contact you (if any). Also, please note that other users of the Services may be able to access or view your Personal Data to the extent that you shared it with those other users.

###  Rights Under the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a "Data Subject" under the GDPR, then in addition to the rights outlined elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, you have the rights outlined in this section. If you have questions about any of these rights or if you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at the physical or digital address below. Also, please note that certain portions of the Services will not work for you unless you provide us with your Personal Data.

  * You have the right to be informed about what data we collect and how we use it.
  * You have the right to request access to your Personal Data.
  * You have the right to have us rectify your Personal Data if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * You have the right to have us erase, remove, or delete, your Personal Data.
  * You have the right to restrict our processing of your Personal Data as provided in the GDPR.
  * You have the right to data portability with respect to your Personal Data.
  * You have the right to object to certain uses of your Personal Data as provided in the GDPR.
  * You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the GDPR.
  * We may transmit your Personal Data outside of the European Union (specifically to the United States of America) for the purposes of data storage and processing and we safeguard the same using agreements with third parties.
  * To the extent you provided consent to our processing of your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. However, such withdrawal will not be effective with respect to lawful processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal. (We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.)
  * We will only retain your Personal Data for as long as necessary for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

##  SECURITY

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information, especially your personally identifiable information and payment information.

However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Further, it is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information and credentials.

##  POWER TO AMEND THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by providing advance notice to you on the Website, through the Services, or through another communication channel. Your continued use after we provide the notice constitutes your consent to the amendment(s).

##  CONTACT

Except as otherwise required, all notices and communications that you may send to us shall be sent to us, with all expenses prepaid, at the following address:

Buyapension.com LLC  
P.O Box 860003  
Shawnee, KS  
66286-0003

You may send informal communications to us via email at tfmetalsreport[at]gmail[dot]com.

_This Privacy Policy is Effective as of October 22, 2018._
